[Money for Nothing by
Dire Straits] ♪ MTV...
[music]
[rustling]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
- When will you be back?
- This evening.
Be careful.
- Well. this coward
couldn't kill me when he had
- the jump on us. damn sure ain't
killing me when we have the jump.
Say it.
I'll be careful.
I love you.
[fireplace burns]
[heavy breathing]
[grunts]
Be back by supper.
Just come back.
[music]
[engine sputters]
Champagne in the morning?
- The sky can't decide if
it's gonna rain or snow.
- I don't want to
be out in either.
- I think we'll waste
this day right here.
[gasps]
[music]
I want some.
Sure you do.
Roll over.
[doorbell rings]
Wait.
My fucking luck.
[doorbell rings]
- I mean it. Wait. I'm
the one who's paying.
[pounding]
I'm fucking coming.
- Banner Creighton.
you're under arrest.
For what?
- Two counts of murder. and
four counts of attempted murder.
Who'd I murder?
And who the fuck did
I attempt to murder?
- Look like you've
seen a ghost. Banner.
And you have.
- If you're arresting
me. arrest him.
- This fucking jackal
hung me by my neck
- and left me to die.
killed my friends
for trespassing.
- And he was well
within his rights.
Turn around.
- At least let me
get fuckin' dressed.
- County jail has got a
brand new suit for you.
[handcuffs fastening]
[door closes]
- I see you brought
your army. Jake.
- You're gonna need
'em. You hear me?
You're gonna fucking need 'em!!!
Nice robe.
Keep smiling. pup.
You cheated death twice.
- You won't cheat
it a third time.
- That sounds a lot like a
confession to me. Banner.
[engine starts]
Woman: Oh. God...
[moaning]
[moaning intensifies]
[music]
We're ready.
Clear 'em out.
Clear back!
[music]
- Jake Dutton... I saw him.
Saw him?
- In town. With the sheriff...
Went to Banner's house.
Did they kill him?
Arrested him.
That was their first mistake.
[music]
[engine starts]
- I'm here to see my
client. Banner Creighton.
That was fast.
Has arraignment been set?
- Eight AM. Tomorrow morning.
Has a judge been assigned?
Uh... Rawlins.
- [knocks]
- Council for 2314.
- We'll post bond
once bail is set.
- They'll not set bail
for a murder charge.
Bail will be set.
Don't speak to anyone.
- Not your cell mate. not
the detectives. no one.
Refer them to me.
- There's two
hookers in my house.
- Can we have them run off
before they rob me blind?
- Is there anything
incriminating in the house?
- I don't know what
incriminating means.
- Any evidence
that would support
their charges against you.
There's nothing at the house.
What's the address?
418 Hancock.
- You really think I'll
be out of here tomorrow?
I'm certain.
[music]
[door closes]
- Arraignment is in the
morning. Rawlins is the judge.
- Make sure he understands
how essential Banner is
to my operations.
I'll find him this evening.
- Mister Creighton mentioned
there are two women
of ill repute in his residence.
- He asked that I remove
them from the premises.
Ill repute?
Prostitutes. sir.
Ah.
Would you like them removed?
I'll remove them.
[jazz music playing]
[women laughing]
[Whitfield laughs]
- Seems like you two don't
need a customer at all.
Who are you?
This is my house.
- I thought it was
Banner's house.
Banner lives here.
But I own it.
It's lovely.
Thank you.
- I assume Banner failed
to pay you before he left.
Not yet.
Does that cover it?
That's too much.
- Well. we haven't
finished yet. have we?
What do you like?
I'm going to show you.
[music]
[sighs]
He's a naughty one.
If you only knew.
[heavy breaths]
[chuckles]
A real naughty one.
[giggles]
Not like that.
Ah!
[gasping]
Like that.
- Just... like that. yes?
Not a sound from you.
I take no pleasure in screams.
[music]
[yelps]
Ah...
[whipping]
[woman shrieks]
Who are you writing?
Spencer.
My youngest.
- Well. he's not mine.
but I call him mine.
- Jack's uncle.
- Yes.
Isn't he coming home?
He is.
- Then... How can you
send him a letter?
I can't.
It's more for me.
- I suppose you could
call it journaling...
- but writing to one's
self seems so narcissistic
I can't bring myself to do it.
- So. I address my
thoughts to him.
What do you tell him?
Everything.
- How I feel. what
I made for supper.
I told him about you.
- Me?
- About the baby.
- How you can tame
Jack with a look.
I would hardly say he's tamed.
- Spencer was always
a very quiet boy.
- Very still. Always watching.
- Deliberate in
everything he did.
- I could jabber away for
hours. and he would just listen.
- I suppose that's
what I'm doing now.
[chuckles]
You do it when they're gone.
Yes.
I think I'm more like Jack.
I need a purpose.
- [groans]
- This waiting suffocates me.
Me too.
- Well. then. you
need a purpose.
My thoughts...
- I have trouble putting
my thoughts into words.
Ah. What then?
- Maybe I'll...
I'll bake a cake.
- You know how to bake a cake?
No.
I can remedy that.
[egg cracks]
[music]
How's this?
All the lumps must be gone.
- I have much more respect for
bakers than I did yesterday.
- There is a measure of
labor that goes into it.
Got caught in the rain?
Little bit.
We're baking a cake.
I see that.
What's the celebration?
You coming home.
We do that every night.
- If you're gonna bake
us cake every evening.
- we're gonna need
bigger horses.
[music]
What happened?
He's where he belongs.
Where does he belong?
- In jail. Awaiting trial.
- Where he will be convicted
and sent to the gallows.
Thank you.
Where's Jack?
- He's right behind me.
putting up the horses.
- Dramatic little
thing. isn't she?
It's like having a new puppy.
- I remember when you
were the new puppy.
No. you don't.
[music]
- Told you there was
nothing to worry about.
You said evening.
I did.
You're late.
I'm a little late.
- I can't wait to see what I get
when I've been gone for a week.
- You're not allowed
to be gone for a week.
[chuckles]
- Calvin Coolidge had two
Grizzly Bears captured
- in Mexico released on
the White House lawn.
Why'd he get them from Mexico?
- He can get all the
grizzlies he wants right here.
- Of all the things in that
headline to disturb you.
- where the bears are from is
the one thing that stands out?
- I'm saying that's a long
way to go for a grizzly.
- It doesn't bother
you he let them loose
on the front yard
of the White House?
- I wouldn't want to be
the man who has to put them
back in their cage.
- Unemployment at historic
lows. down to 2.4 percent.
Where?
Not here.
- New commission formed in
Washington to regulate mining.
CEO of Anaconda Copper
Mines appointed chairman.
Whitfield.
- Westfield Silver Mining CEO
Donald Whitfield. vice-chair...
- They put the bosses
of the mining companies
- in charge of
regulating the mines?
- That should tell you
all you need to know
about politics. son.
You're in politics.
I'm in law enforcement.
- You enforce the
laws you push through.
Jack.
- I ain't complaining. I'm just
saying it's the same thing.
- You're a cattleman in
charge of regulating cattle.
Am I wrong?
- There's this theory that
these scientists came up with
- after studying tribes
in India and Africa.
and South America.
- The smaller tribes
didn't have any government.
Didn't need any.
- They could sit down and
talk out their problems.
- decide where to
plant crops. to hunt.
- They was just a
big family. really.
- But when the number of people
got up around five hundred.
- if there wasn't any
government. the strongest people
- would take advantage
of the weakest...
- Every time. Without fail.
- They would
enslave. rape. steal.
- Enrich their lives at the
expense of other people's lives.
- Government is
man's way of trying
to control our behavior.
- But it can't be
controlled. it's what we are.
- Sooner or later. the
kind of people who would
- enrich themselves
at your expense.
- will use the
government to do it.
- And mark my words.
one day they'll create
- laws to control what
we say. how we think.
- They will outlaw
our right to disagree.
if we let them.
- I created the commission to
protect the way this family
provides for itself...
How it protects the land.
- Isn't Whitfield
doing the same thing?
The exact same thing.
Unfortunately for him.
- what's good for his way of
life is not good for ours.
What about right and wrong?
- No such thing.
Can't think that way.
- You can only think about
what's good for this ranch.
- What's good for your
family. that's it.
Then use their rules to do it.
A bear in the White House.
- Of all the things that
happen in the world each day.
- why is the news
telling you that?
- What aren't they telling
you. that's the question.
- This isn't the news.
Jack. This is camouflage.
- We don't talk
politics at the table.
- If you know what's good for
you. you'll remember that.
[music]
How'd we both get in trouble?
- Banner in jail
doesn't solve anything.
- This fight ain't
over. It's just begun.
She's not mad...
she's scared.
[music]
[horse approaching]
[wind blowing]
[music]
Speak English. boy?
I speak English.
What are you doing out here?
Tending sheep.
I don't see any sheep.
- That's why I'm
looking for 'em.
- Sounds like you
strayed from the flock.
- Flock strayed from me
while I was sleeping.
I've seen no sheep tracks.
- Not following them.
I'm headed to water.
That's where they'll be.
How old are you?
What do you care?
You should be in school.
Finished school.
Where?
Kansas.
What's the name?
- I don't have to
answer your questions.
- You'll answer them or get drug
back to the school by your hair.
You don't have the right.
[grunting]
- No telling which school
this one escaped from.
- Doesn't matter. He's
headed to ours. now.
- I'll run this one
back. You keep going.
- Where there's
one there's more.
Maybe a whole camp of 'em.
Wherever they are...
she is.
I'll take him back.
I'm a man of the cloth.
- Which is to say.
I'm a man of my word.
Ah! Ah!
[music]
Heeya.
- I served a mission
in Argentina.
Served one in Peru.
The Philippines.
- All populated with
people like you.
People who now thrive.
They thrive.
Build cities.
Grow crops.
All in the bosom of Christ.
- They followed our
teachings and they prosper.
You...
reject them.
Fight them.
And suffering is your reward.
- Salvation awaits in the light.
and yet...
you people...
choose darkness.
Seek it.
Crave it.
- I think your souls have
been spoken for already.
I think the devil has them.
You don't need schools.
You need exorcisms.
You are a priest?
I am.
A holy man.
Yes.
But you've killed.
In the name of God.
Stolen.
What have I stolen?
The land you sit on.
I have stolen nothing.
- If you hadn't stolen
it. you wouldn't be here.
You'd be somewhere else.
- I don't understand
your pagan logic.
Your God has all these laws.
I know them.
I studied them.
- You're supposed
to teach His laws.
- but you break
them to teach them.
- So. the laws means
nothing to you.
Which means...
- Your God doesn't
exist. and you know it.
[music]
- Blasphemy. You
godless heathen.
- I think the world will be a
better place without you in it.
Without any of you.
Our Father. who art in Heaven.
Look at me when I speak!
Hallowed be thy name.
- Thy kingdom come.
Thy will be done.
On Earth as it is in Heaven...
[screams]
- If his will is done on earth.
and my knife is to your throat.
- this must be what
your God wants.
[gurgles]
Can you walk?
I can run if you want.
We let the horses run.
- There's two more priests
looking for Teonna.
I saw the tracks.
Which way did they go?
Hank in the badlands?
By the Red Creek.
They will stop for the night.
We won't.
What do we do with him?
[music]
Go wait with the horses.
What did you do?
Ate his soul.
- We must ride fast. Keep up.
He...
[sheep bleats]
Man: Boy!
[music]
- This one's school
age. as well.
- Well. at least
he's got a vocation.
Tending sheep is God's work.
- We are looking for
a girl. About fifteen.
Why looking for her?
Broke the law.
What law?
- We owe you no
explanation. child.
Have you seen a girl?
I've seen no girl.
[music]
[priest grunts]
[Teonna shouts]
[clothes ripping]
[priest growls]
Ah!
Let me see.
[gasping]
The girl has blinded you.
You godless witch!
You'll kill her. brother.
With God as my witness.
Aah!
[music]
[gasping]
- Wait...
He beat you up pretty good.
Can you stand?
[music]
[gunshot]
Goddam your fucking soul.
[screams]
[sobs]
[music]
- I'll have a skiff run
you in. It'll be faster.
- I can do without customs
boarding the vessel.
Understood.
I'm in your debt.
You're in no such thing.
- I think perhaps the sea
is the last place where men
- do the right thing
for that reason alone.
- Maybe the whole world
should be put to sea.
Whole world would drown.
- If ever I find myself in
the company of a leopard.
I'd appreciate some assistance.
- I didn't tell
you I was a hunter.
You're famous. Spencer Dutton.
In case you are unaware.
I'm becoming aware.
Speaking of wild cats.
- you've a tiger by the
tail with your new bride.
[music]
- Mussolini's not a fan
folks carrying guns.
- Different rules in Sicily.
but if you go inland.
- you'll need to
hide that thing.
- Mafia won't like it
too much either. though.
What's the mafia?
- Stay here long
you'll find out. mate.
Thank you.
Let's find a hotel.
- Spoken like a man who
thinks he's in control.
- Let's find a cafe.
I need pasta and wine.
[chatter]
- Deep down you love
being told what to do.
There's a freedom in it.
- And we all know
how you Americans
feel about your freedom.
Hey.
I'll follow you...
- but I ain't
walking behind you.
- You sure? It's a
pretty good view.
- If I was a betting man.
I'd bet you're smiling.
You booked us passage?
We leave on Thursday.
You're not eating.
I'm not hungry.
How is that possible?
- Don't know. Just ain't.
- You've become the
lions you hunted.
- Gorging yourself on a kill
then sleeping in the sun
- for a week till you muster
the energy to bed a lioness.
- I won't wait a week.
I'll have you know.
[music]
- This is the first time
I've been in a restaurant
- with somebody
since I left Montana.
Pesky. these demons of yours.
- The further we move from danger
the more we'll see them. I fear.
- We're not moving
further from danger.
Eat. I demand it.
What is it?
Rice.
- Don't look like rice.
- [laughs]
- It's rice rolled
in flour and fried.
How do you know the food here?
I'm British.
- All we do is travel the
world and become experts
on the places we visit.
That don't make sense.
Like I said. I'm British.
- So. your culture is based
on pretending to be experts
- on things you
know nothing about.
No. baby.
That's the French.
[chuckles]
Made you smile.
My Holy Grail.
- You need loftier goals.
- No. I don't.
Eat.
Well?
Pretty good.
Experts. I told you.
[music]
Man: Alexandra?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today